[Music]
we were curious what people wanted to
know about Joe burrow I guess a little
bit outside of the athlete so we googled
you know I guess some of the most asked
questions yeah and we just want to ask
you a couple of those okay if you
wouldn't mind so the first one and again
this is based on real data that people
are wondering about you does Joe burrow
have a necklace collection
I wouldn't call it a collection but I
have several yes the most notable I've
seen is the Nike one with the diamonds
yeah I think that's the one where like
you know when we talk about your ice
yeah I have a couple that are bigger
that are probably you gotta be more
specific in the situation that you wear
it that I haven't really shown to the
world no you can't just you can't just
put on the big German Nike I mean you
can't just walk around with a five pound
Iced Out necklace no you need to be
Lordstown shoot right you're smart you
know that you need you know it's based
on the scenario based on location
situation exactly that's when you pick
your eyes all right uh the next question
you know professional athlete you know
you care a lot about what you put into
your body what you do to your body so
the internet wants to know does Joe
burrow have a chef I do you do have a
chef so what kind of I guess is are
there any regulars that you would ask
your Chef to prepare for you like what's
in your diet so I like chicken with
peppers and onions and rice that's my
main go-to but I usually just let him
whip it up because that he's great at it
nice
um he knows what I like if I don't like
it I'll tell him but he knows what I
like and he does a great job for him
very cool well speaking of food
this one shocked me that there was this
many people to where this was like we
are really curious if this is a thing
does Joe burrow like turkey not on
Thanksgiving really no what's your
Thanksgiving Day ham ham big wow yeah
see I I avoid the ham I'm anti-turkey
anti-turkey that is super interesting so
hot take he does not like turkey exactly
very interesting so where does Joe
burrow keep his Heisman Trophy
sounds like somebody that wants to steal
it to me right next to the front door
they want the code to in my garage too
apparently it's in a very secure trophy
case in my basement with other trophies
I'm assuming yeah very good people are
curious if you have a suit collection or
how many suits you own
I probably have 15 suits can't you gotta
can't wear the same thing no oh more
than two times
cannot so I'm gonna have to get some
more this year for sure yeah I'm aware
of your fandom for SpongeBob SquarePants
one of my favorite things about you is
SpongeBob like the socks I've seen this
I got a pocket square for one I have the
shoes I think that's probably the extent
of my SpongeBob
performance SpongeBob yes there's a
whole informal collection we don't have
to get into that it's a whole thing the
internet wants to know if Joe burrow was
voted most athletic and most likely to
be famous in high school
I think so were you voted you were voted
most athletic for sure did you perform
with Kid Cudi on stage I guess
technically yes I didn't have a mic but
I was definitely singing this song you
were present yeah it wasn't that I mean
if somebody would have handed you a mic
you would have gladly yes I would have
all right well that's good to hear have
you ever wanted to play other positions
besides quarterbacks such as running
back receiver were you ever interested
in any other position when I first
started in third grade I wanted to be a
running back I got upset that my coach
made me play quarterback why did he make
you play quarterback
I don't know I guess I was a coach's kid
and he was like you're a quarterback and
so that's the start of my quarterbacking
career wow yeah very cool so you want to
do what what Drew you to being a running
back and well I knew that I mean I was
what are you eight years old in third
grade yeah I knew we weren't going to be
throwing the ball a lot oh yeah that's
true when you're eight so I just wanted
to have the ball right
[Music]